A Guide to the Lucille P. Markey Charitable Trust records FA017
Rockefeller Archive Center
Lucille P. Markey Charitable Trust records
1931-1998
Rockefeller Archive Center
Lucille P. Markey Charitable Trust
FA017
2.2 Cubic Feet 155 reels of 35mm microfilm
Conditions Governing Access
Open for scholarly research without restriction.
Arrangement note
The Lucille P. Markey Charitable Trust collection is arranged in six series:
Series 1 - Scholars and Visiting Fellows
Series 2 - Institutional Grants and Proposals
Series 3 - Governance
Series 4 - Program Development
Series 5 - Correspondence
Series 6 - Scrapbook, Photographs and Miscellany
Biographical/Historical note
Institutional Background
The Lucile P. Markey Charitable Trust (Markey Trust) was established as a limited term trust in the will of Lucille P. Markey in 1975. Incorporated as a Florida nonprofit organization 501(C)(3) status, the Trust began operation in October 1983. The Trust's office opened in Miami on January 1, 1984.
Mrs. Markey had several specific goals for her charitable giving which defined the nature of the Trust. Wishing to distribute the grant money in a relatively short period of time in order to fund current research, she was advised to create a charitable, limited term trust. Mrs. Markey wanted her fortune to be dedicated to the pursuit of "human health," which meant that trust contributions specifically targeted "basic biomedical research."
To ensure that her assets were distributed as she intended, Mrs. Markey nominated several close associates as trustees. Her attorney, Louis J. Hector, chaired the Board of Trustees, and Robert B. Glaser, M.D., became the Director of Medical Science. Other trustees included: William Sutter, representing Hopkins and Sutter, attorneys for Mrs. Markey's first husband Warren Wright; Laurette Heraty, Warren Wright's former secretary; and Margaret B. Glass, an employee of Calumet Farm. George Shinn subsequently replaced Laurette Heraty as board member.
During its fifteen-year operation, the Trust distributed over $500 million in three broad categories: Individual Grants, including scholarships and fellowships to younger researchers; Research Program Grants, to research centers conducting advanced research; and General Organizational Grants, toward the training and education of Ph.D.s and M.D.s pursuing careers in biomedical research.
Scholars received funding for up to three years' postdoctoral study and were offered a subsequent five years of support for faculty positions including salary and research funds. The first class of scholars began its tenure in July 1985. The final class selected (the seventh class overall) began its term in July 1991. Over the fifteen-year period of the Trust, 113 scholars were awarded grants. A comprehensive history of the Markey Trust is included in the Trust's Final Report, 1983-1996.
Limited Term Trust
At the time of its creation,the Lucille P. Markey Charitable Trust's financial reserves placed it among the ten largest foundations in terms of charitable distribution. The terms of the Trust and its management of assets were explained in "Closing a Foundation: The Lucille P. Markey Charitable Trust" (Washington, D.C.: Council on Foundations, 2000), by John H. Dickason, and Duncan Neuhauser, available in the Rockefeller Archive Center's library collection.
The National Research Council Committee for the Evaluation of the Lucille P. Markey Visiting Fellows Program issued two publications concerning the Scholars Program: "Evaluation of the Markey Scholars Program" (2006) and "Bridging the Bed-Bunch Gap: Contributions of the Markey Trust" (2004) (both Washington, DC: National Academies Press).
The unique combination of the successful scholars selection process and the designation of the charitable trust as a limited term endeavor inspired several National Research Council reviews of the comprehensive program, including: Krystyna R. Isaacs, "The Lucille P. Markey Charitable Trust Scholars Program: Enhancing Philanthropy's Support of Biomedical Science"; and National Research Council, "Committee for the Evaluation of the Lucille P. Markey Charitable Trust Programs in Biomedical Sciences" (both Washington, DC: National Academies Press, 2006).
Biographical Note
Lucille Parker was born on December 14, 1896, near Tollesboro, Kentucky; she was the youngest of seven children and the daughter of a tobacco farmer. In 1918, Lucille married Warren Wright, Sr., who had inherited the Calumet Baking Powder Company, as well as a horse farm near Lexington, Kentucky. The Wrights built this small inheritance into one of the most successful thoroughbred horse breeding and racing stables, Calumet Farm. After the death of Warren Wright in 1950, Lucille assumed control of the Farm. The bulk of Mrs. Markey's estate, however, derived from a large investment in oil and gas leases inherited from Warren Wright and drilled on the Waddell Ranch in western Texas.
Lucille Wright married her second husband, Admiral Gene Markey, in 1952 and continued to pursue her passion in horse breeding and horse racing. Over a period of nearly 50 years, Calumet won 8 Kentucky Derbies, 2 Triple Crowns, 3 Filly Triple Crowns, and had 148 stakes winners with total earnings of over $26 million.
During the reign of Calumet Farms, Mrs. Markey's charitable giving focused on the Bluegrass Boys' Ranch in Kentucky and the establishment of a cancer center at the University of Kentucky. The establishment of the Trust enabled Mrs. Markey to extend her interests in health to general support of biomedical institutions, with an emphasis on research, as opposed to health care delivery.
Mrs. Markey died on July 24, 1982. After Mrs. Markey's death, the Farm was inherited by Warren Wright, Jr.'s heirs. Mismanagement led to the forced sale of all land, horses, and equipment in 1992, when Calumet Farm filed for bankruptcy.
Mrs. Markey's second husband Admiral Gene Markey was a writer, producer, and Hollywood personality who achieved some notoriety in his personal life, if not in his attempt to become a recognized writer. Prior to his marriage to Lucille, he was married to three well-known actresses: Myrna Loy, Hedy Lamarr, and Joan Bennett. The papers of Admiral Gene Markey are housed at Skidmore College in Saratoga Springs, New York, and include the Markeys' personal library of horse literature.
File Plan note
Former Classification: XIV
Scope and Contents
The collection focuses upon grants awarded for biomedical research to institutions in the United States during 1983-1996. Grant records include correspondence regarding application criteria, financial awards, and periodic research reports. Administrative records detail program development and advisory committee decisions. A scrapbook, newspaper clippings, and photographs detail Calumet Farm, the horseracing concern which Mrs. Markey owned and operated.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
The archival material has been reformatted and the original records are no longer available. User copies of the microfilm are available for scholarly access.
Appraisal
The archival material has been reformatted and the original records are no longer available. User copies of the microfilm are available for scholarly access.
Medical research; Biology -- Research; Lucille P. Markey Charitable Trust
- Scholars and Visiting Fellows, 1983-1998; 1
  Arrangement note
  This series is arranged in four subseries:
  Subseries 1 - Scholar Applicants
  Subseries 2 - Visiting Fellow Applicants
  Subseries 3 - Selection Committee
  Subseries 4 - Annual Conferences
  - Scholar Applicants, 1983-1998; 1
    This subseries is arranged in two sections:
    Section A - Grants
    Section B - Denied Applicants
    - Grants, 1983-1998; A
      This section is arranged alphabetically by the last name of the grant recipient.
      Scope and Contents note
      This subseries includes files for the 113 scholars awarded grants to pursue basic biomedical research. Scholars' grants were awarded to individuals at the initial stages of their pursuit of study in postgraduate biomedical research. Each grant file is titled with the grantee's name followed by the grant number which indicates the year in which the grant began. The inclusive dates note the chronology of the reports and correspondence. Each file includes: scholar's transmittal sheet; statement of research goals; letters of recommendation from faculty sponsor, department chairperson or institutional officer, director of PhD training program or residency program director; and other letters of endorsement from colleagues and mentors.
      Each grant file includes a checklist of documents required to complete the application packet. In cases where there are several grant numbers for one individual, the application is located in the first file. Each file is subdivided as follows: Application; Award, Fund and Term Letters; Grant Data, including financial information; and Reports and Correspondence, which includes annual research reports submitted by the grantee and other correspondence pertaining to the status of the research project funded.
      - Anderson, James M. - Grant 88-39 (Reel 1, Frame 1)
      - Axelsen, Paul H. - Grant 89-27 (Reel 1, Frame 233)
      - Axelsen, Paul H. - Grant 93-24 (Reel 1, Frame 433)
      - Baraban, Jay M. - Grant 85-2 (Reel 1, Frame 503)
      - Bargmann, Cornelia I. - Grant 90-34 (Reel 1, Frame 771)
      - Bargmann, Cornelia I. - Grant 91-51 (Reel 1, Frame 879)
      - Baron, Margaret H. - Grant 87-24 (Reel 2, Frame 1)
      - Barsh, Gregory S. - Grant 89-26 (Reel 2, Frame 368)
      - Beechem, Joseph M. - Grant 88-31 (Reel 2, Frame 468)
      - Beechem, Joseph M. - Grant 89-33 (Reel 2, Frame 555)
      - Benjamin, Howard - Grant 90-31 (Reel 2, Frame 712)
      - Benjamin, Howard - Grant 92-31 (Reel 2, Frame 827)
      - Bonadio, Jeffrey - Grant - 86-21 (Reel 2, Frame 947)
      - Braiman, Mark S. - Grant 86-16 (Reel 2, Frame 1023)
      - Braiman, Mark S. - Grant 8853 (Reel 2, Frame 1158)
      - Brandt, Stephen J. - Grant 86-22 (Reel 3, Frame 1)
      - Brandt, Stephen J. - Grant 88-2 (Reel 3, Frame 120)
      - Brandt, Stephen J. - Grant 90-38 (Reel 3, Frame 244)
      - Brown, Patrick - Grant 85-3 (Reel 3, Frame 397)
      - Cleary, Michael L. - Grant 85-4 (Reel 3, Frame 538)
      - Cooper, John A. - Grant 87-28 (Reel 3, Frame 813)
      - Crews, Stephen T. - Grant 85-10 (Reel 3, Frame 1062)
      - Crews, Stephen T. - Grant 88-4 (Reel 3, Frame 1200)
      - Cross, Frederick R. - Grant 88-38 (Reel 4, Frame 1)
      - Cross, Frederick R. - Grant 89-38 (Reel 4, Frame 91)
      - Cyert, Martha S. - Grant 91-40 (Reel 4, Frame 244)
      - Cyert, Martha S. - Grant 92-42 (Reel 4, Frame 332)
      - D'Andrea, Alan D. - Grant 90-24 (Reel 4, Frame 477)
      - D'Andrea, Alan D. - Grant 90-46 (Reel 4, Frame 533)
      - Darst, Seth A. - Grant 90-32 (Reel 4, Frame 696)
      - Darst, Seth A. - Grant 93-17 (Reel 4, Frame 831)
      - Davis, Laura I. - Grant 90-35 (Reel 4, Frame 985)
      - Davitz, Michael A. - Grant 88-25 (Reel 5, Frame 1)
      - de Lange, Titia - Grant 87-15 (Reel 5, Frame 227)
      - de Lange, Titia - Grant 90-37 (Reel 5, Frame 350)
      - Deshaies, Raymond J. - Grant 90-27 (Reel 5, Frame 503)
      - Deshaies, Raymond J. - Grant 94-9 (Reel 5, Frame 648)
      - DiNardo, Stephen - Grant 86-14 (Reel 5, Frame 768)
      - DiNardo, Stephen - Grant 88-58 (Reel 5, Frame 898)
      - Doudna, Jennifer A. - Grant 91-42 (Reel 6, Frame 1)
      - Doudna, Jennifer A. - Grant 95-9 (Reel 6, Frame 156)
      - Doupe, Allison - Grant 90-22 (Reel 6, Frame 247)
      - Doupe, Allison - Grant 93-19 (Reel 6, Frame 389)
      - Dunphy, William G. - Grant 87-16 (Reel 6, Frame 512)
      - Dunphy, William G. - Grant 89-39 (Reel 6, Frame 622)
      - Duyk, Geoffrey M. - Grant 91-31 (Reel 6, Frame 795)
      - Edgar, Bruce A. - Grant 90-28 (Reel 6, Frame 874)
      - Edgar, Bruce A. - Grant 93-18 (Reel 6, Frame 1020)
      - Ellenberger, Thomas E. - Grant 91-33 (Reel 7, Frame 1)
      - Engel, Joanne N. - Grant 88-36 (Reel 7, Frame 207)
      - Figge, James J. - Grant 89-21 (Reel 7, Frame 489)
      - Figge, James J. - Grant 90-18 (Reel 7, Frame 573)
      - Friend, Stephen H. - Grant 87-25 (Reel 7, Frame 726)
      - Fuller, Robert S. - Grant 86-13 (Reel 8, Frame 1)
      - Fuller, Robert S. - Grant 87-31 (Reel 8, Frame 118)
      - Gabriel, Abram - Grant 91-30 (Reel 8, Frame 318)
      - Gabriel, Abram - Grant 92-41 (Reel 8, Frame 405)
      - Gelles, Jeff - Grant 88-28 (Reel 8, Frame 534)
      - Gelles, Jeff - Grant 89-31 (Reel 8, Frame 625)
      - George, Alfred L., Jr. - Grant 91-29 (Reel 8, Frame 790)
      - George, Alfred L., Jr. - Grant 92-40 (Reel 8, Frame 928)
      - Glass, Christopher - Grant 87-23 (Reel 9, Frame 1)
      - Goldin, Alan L. - Grant 87-22 (Reel 9, Frame 266)
      - Goldin, Alan L. - Grant 88-57 (Reel 9, Frame 355)
      - Goldman, Adrian - Grant 87-17 (Reel 9, Frame 551)
      - Goldman, Adrian - Grant 88-51 (Reel 9, Frame 714)
      - Green, Eric D. - Grant 90-26 (Reel 9, Frame 919)
      - Grossman, Alan D. - Grant 86-17 (Reel 10, Frame 1)
      - Grossman, Alan D. - Grant 88-54 (Reel 10, Frame 110)
      - Hall, Kathleen B. - Grant 88-30 (Reel 10, Frame 296)
      - Hall, Kathleen B. - Grant 90-47 (Reel 10, Frame 401)
      - Han, Min - Grant 91-41 (Reel 10, Frame 586)
      - Han, Min - Grant 92-12 (Reel 10, Frame 659)
      - Hardin, Jeffrey D. - Grant 90-29 (Reel 10, Frame 812)
      - Hardin, Jeffrey D. - Grant 91-48 (Reel 10, Frame 897)
      - Havran, Wendy L. - Grant 89-19 (Reel 11, Frame 1)
      - Havran, Wendy L. - Grant 91-57 (Reel 11, Frame 120)
      - Herman, Gail E. - Grant 87-27 (Reel 11, Frame 261)
      - Herschlag, Daniel - Grant 90-30 (Reel 11, Frame 532)
      - Herschlag, Daniel - Grant 92-43 (Reel 11, Frame 650)
      - Herz, Joachim J. - Grant 91-35 (Reel 11, Frame 783)
      - Hockenbery, David M. - Grant 91-28 (Reel 11, Frame 991)
      - Hockenbery, David M. - Grant 92-35 (Reel 11, Frame 1080)
      - Hoekstra, Merl F. - Grant 88-37 (Reel 12, Frame 1)
      - Hoekstra, Merl F. - Grant 89-32 (Reel 12, Frame 95)
      - Hyman, Anthony - Grant 88-8 (Reel 12, Frame 245)
      - Hyman, Anthony - Grant 91-38 (Reel 12, Frame 328)
      - Jacks, Tyler E. - Grant 91-36 (Reel 12, Frame 437)
      - Jacks, Tyler E. - Grant 92-34 (Reel 12, Frame 517)
      - Jay, Daniel G. - Grant 88-33 (Reel 12, Frame 597)
      - Kadonaga, James T. - Grant 87-14 (Reel 12, Frame 817)
      - Kadonaga, James T. - Grant 88-50 (Reel 12, Frame 908)
      - Kaiser, Chris A. - Grant 90-33 (Reel 13, Frame 1)
      - Kaiser, Chris A. - Grant 91-23 (Reel 13, Frame 85)
      - Katz, Lawrence C. - Grant 86-26 (Reel 13, Frame 250)
      - Katz, Lawrence C. - Grant 91-20 (Reel 13, Frame 437)
      - Kelly, Carolyn J. - Grant 86-19 (Reel 13, Frame 504)
      - Kelly, Daniel P. - Grant 89-25 (Reel 13, Frame 756)
      - Kim, Stuart K. - Grant 88-29 (Reel 13, Frame 965)
      - Kim, Stuart K. - Grant 89-37 (Reel 13, Frame 1045)
      - Kingsley, David M. - Grant 89-18 (Reel 14, Frame 1)
      - Kingsley, David M. - Grant 92-13 (Reel 14, Frame 128)
      - Konarska, M. Magda - Grant 87-19 (Reel 14, Frame 267)
      - Konarska, M. Magda - Grant 89-36 (Reel 14, Frame 380)
      - Kopito, Ron R. - Grant 85-11 (Reel 14, Frame 543)
      - Kopito, Ron R. - Grant 87-4 (Reel 14, Frame 666)
      - Koshland, Douglas E. - Grant 85-12 (Reel 14, Frame 864)
      - Koshland, Douglas E. - Grant 87-1 (Reel 14, Frame 963)
      - Koshland, Douglas E. - Grant 87-30 (Reel 14, Frame 1003)
      - Krasnow, Mark A. - Grant 87-29 (Reel 15, Frame 1)
      - Kurilla, Michael G. - Grant 89-24 (Reel 15, Frame 208)
      - Kurilla, Michael G. - Grant 91-52 (Reel 15, Frame 324)
      - Lassar, Andrew - Grant 87-20 (Reel 15, Frame 460)
      - Lassar, Andrew - Grant 91-50 (Reel 15, Frame 621)
      - Lerner, Ethan A. - Grant 86-23 (Reel 15, Frame 766)
      - Li, Ellen - Grant 85-5 (Reel 16, Frame 1)
      - Li, Joachim J. - Grant 90-19 (Reel 16, Frame 260)
      - Lieber, Michael R. - Grant 88-52 (Reel 16, Frame 495)
      - Lieber, Michael R. - Grant 89-34 (Reel 16, Frame 588)
      - Lieber, Michael R. - Grant 89-34 Extended (Reel 16, Frame 755)
      - Madison, Daniel V. - Grant 87-21 (Reel 16, Frame 806)
      - Madison, Daniel V. - Grant 89-7 (Reel 16, Frame 917)
      - Margolis, Benjamin L. - Grant 90-23 (Reel 17, Frame 1)
      - Margolis, Benjamin L. - Grant 95-36 (Reel 17, Frame 183)
      - McClelland, Michael - Grant 85-13 (Reel 17, Frame 219)
      - McClelland, Michael - Grant 87-2 (Reel 17, Frame 298)
      - Meister, Markus - Grant 89-17 (Reel 17, Frame 509)
      - Meister, Markus - Grant 91-56 (Reel 17, Frame 621)
      - Minden, Jonathan S. - Grant 89-16 (Reel 17, Frame 776)
      - Minden, Jonathan S. - Grant 91-9 (Reel 17, Frame 869)
      - Montell, Denise J. - Grant 91-43 (Reel 18, Frame 1)
      - Montell, Denise J. - Grant 92-39 (Reel 18, Frame 86)
      - Murray, Andrew W. - Grant 86-15 (Reel 18, Frame 220)
      - Osborne, Timothy F. - Grant 86-11 (Reel 18, Frame 513)
      - Osborne, Timothy F. - Grant 91-8 (Reel 18, Frame 693)
      - Palazzolo, Michael J. - Grant 88-27 (Reel 18, Frame 808)
      - Palazzolo, Michael J. - Grant 91-13 (Reel 18, Frame 938)
      - Palazzolo, Michael J. - Grant 91-58 (Reel 18, Frame 992)
      - Perrimon, Norbert - Grant 85-14 (Reel 19, Frame 1)
      - Petri, William A., Jr. - Grant 85-6 (Reel 19, Frame 113)
      - Reed, Robin E. - Grant 88-34 (Reel 19, Frame 447)
      - Reed, Sharon L. - Grant 85-7 (Reel 19, Frame 678)
      - Reitman, Marc L. - Grant 89-23 (Reel 20, Frame 1)
      - Reitman, Marc L. - Grant 93-9 (Reel 20, Frame 154)
      - Relman, David A. - Grant 90-21 (Reel 20, Frame 266)
      - Rembold, Christopher M. - Grant 86-25 (Reel 20, Frame 515)
      - Retzinger, Gregory S. - Grant 86-18 (Reel 20, Frame 738)
      - Retzinger, Gregory S. - Grant 87-34 (Reel 20, Frame 868)
      - Rio, Donald C. - Grant 86-12 (Reel 21, Frame 1)
      - Rio, Donald C. - Grant 87-6 (Reel 21, Frame 71)
      - Rio, Donald C. - Grant 92-30 (Reel 21, Frame 243)
      - Roberts, James M. - Grant 87-26 (Reel 21, Frame 371)
      - Sakaguchi, Shimon - Grant 86-24 (Reel 21, Frame 496)
      - Sakaguchi, Shimon - Grant 88-3 (Reel 21, Frame 592)
      - Sakaguchi, Shimon - Grant 89-35 (Reel 21, Frame 677)
      - Sakaguchi, Shimon - Grant 92-19 (Reel 21, Frame 813)
      - Scheinberg, David A. - Grant 88-23 (Reel 21, Frame 893)
      - Schmid, Sandra L. - Grant 87-18 (Reel 22, Frame 1)
      - Schmid, Sandra L. - Grant 89-5 (Reel 22, Frame 117)
      - Schwartz, David C. - Grant 88-24 (Reel 22, Frame 277)
      - Schwartz, David C. - Grant 90-14 (Reel 22, Frame 371)
      - Semenza, Gregg L. - Grant 89-22 (Reel 22, Frame 568)
      - Sharpe, Arlene H. - Grant 8620 (Reel 22, Frame 752)
      - Sharpe, Arlene H. - Grant 91-53 (Reel 22, Frame 986)
      - Sheares, Bradley T. - Grant 85-15 (Reel 23, Frame 1)
      - Simon, Michael A. - Grant 89-15 (Reel 23, Frame 125)
      - Simon, Michael A. - Grant 92-44 (Reel 23, Frame 251)
      - Sorger, Peter K. - Grant 91-37 (Reel 23, Frame 360)
      - Sorger, Peter K. - Grant 93-23 (Reel 23, Frame 472)
      - Sorscher, Eric J. - Grant 89-20 (Reel 23, Frame 584)
      - Stock, Ann - Grant 89-14 (Reel 23, Frame 851)
      - Stock, Ann - Grant 90-13 (Reel 23, Frame 926)
      - Stock, Ann - Grant 91-54 (Reel 23, Frame 1006)
      - Tepper, Robert I. - Grant 90-20 (Reel 24, Frame 1)
      - Tepper, Robert I. - Grant 90-48 (Reel 24, Frame 67)
      - Tessier-Lavigne, Marc - Grant 89-13 (Reel 24, Frame 199)
      - Tessier-Lavigne, Marc - Grant 91-47 (Reel 24, Frame 317)
      - Van Etten, Richard A. - Grant 90-25 (Reel 24, Frame 445)
      - Van Etten, Richard A. - Grant 91-59 (Reel 24, Frame 525)
      - Wasserman, Steven A. - Grant 85-16 (Reel 24, Frame 674)
      - Wasserman, Steven A. - Grant 87-32 (Reel 24, Frame 786)
      - Waters, M. Gerard - Grant 91-3 (Reel 24, Frame 963)
      - Waters, M. Gerard - Grant 92-11 (Reel 24, Frame 1037)
      - Weis, Janis J. - Grant 85-17 (Reel 25, Frame 2)
      - Weis, Janis J. - Grant 89-6 (Reel 25, Frame 195)
      - Weiser, Jeffrey N. - Grant 91-32 (Reel 25, Frame 286)
      - Weiser, Jeffrey N. - Grant 92-37 (Reel 25, Frame 372)
      - Whitman, Malcolm R. - Grant 89-12 (Reel 25, Frame 489)
      - Wolin, Sandra L. - Grant 88-32 (Reel 25, Frame 710)
      - Woods, Jon P. - Grant 91-34 (Reel 25, Frame 827)
      - Woods, Jon P. - Grant 94-2 (Reel 25, Frame 971)
      - Yancopoulos, George D. - Grant 88-40 (Reel 26, Frame 1)
      - Yarmush, Martin L. - Grant 85-9 (Reel 26, Frame 72)
      - Yarmush, Martin L. - Grant 88-55 (Reel 26, Frame 280)
      - Yen, Tim J. - Grant 89-11 (Reel 26, Frame 484)
      - Yen, Tim J. - Grant 90-39 (Reel 26, Frame 564)
      - Young, John Ding-E. - Grant 85-8 (Reel 26, Frame 718)
    - Denied Applicants, 1984-1990; B
      This section is arranged by application number.
      Applications from individuals who were not accepted to the Scholars Program at the time of application. Some applicants may have applied to the Program more than once. Applications were originally ordered by number, indicating the year of application.
      - Muneoka, Ken - Application 840001 (Reel 27, Frame 1)
      - Berry, James O. - Application 840003 (Reel 27, Frame 34)
      - Roy, Dilip G. - Application 840004 (Reel 27, Frame 65)
      - Daniels, Frederick H. - Application 840009 (Reel 27, Frame 95)
      - Elliott, Glen - Application 840010 (Reel 27, Frame 135)
      - Ganellen, Ronald J. - Application 840011 (Reel 27, Frame 140)
      - Jenson, Hal B. - Application 840015 (Reel 27, Frame 148)
      - Moore, Steven A. - Application 840017 (Reel 27, Frame 184)
      - Muntz, Kathryn - Application 840018 (Reel 27, Frame 226)
      - Storthz, Karen A. - Application 840021 (Reel 27, Frame 236)
      - Tamburini, Paul P. - Application 840022 (Reel 27, Frame 263)
      - Chan, Thomas C. K. - Application 840026 (Reel 27, Frame 299)
      - Baggett, Jack M. - Application 840027 (Reel 27, Frame 333)
      - Badamchian, Mahnaz - Application 840028 (Reel 27, Frame 370)
      - Hoshi, Hiroyoshi - Application 840029 (Reel 27, Frame 409)
      - Chalovich, Joseph M. - Application 840030 (Reel 27, Frame 432)
      - Hoffman, Maureane - Application 840031 (Reel 27, Frame 465)
      - Wessinger, William D. - Application 840032 (Reel 27, Frame 493)
      - Pixley, Robin S. - Application 840033 (Reel 27, Frame 528)
      - Matt, Kathleen S. - Application 840034 (Reel 27, Frame 554)
      - Marcelletti, John F. - Application 840035 (Reel 27, Frame 597)
      - Nonaka, Makoto - Application 840036 (Reel 27, Frame 626)
      - Larson, Susan G. - Application 840037 (Reel 27, Frame 664)
      - Plous, Roneley H. - Application 840038 (Reel 27, Frame 695)
      - Williams, Michael E. - Application 840039 (Reel 27, Frame 720)
      - Yellon, Steven M. - Application 840040 (Reel 27, Frame 759)
      - Dylewski, Daniel P. - Application 840041 (Reel 27, Frame 790)
      - Billingsley, Melvin L. - Application 840042 (Reel 27, Frame 825)
      - Lustig, Robert H. - Application 840043 (Reel 27, Frame 864)
      - Sasaki, Seiichi - Application 840045 (Reel 27, Frame 895)
      - Breitwieser, Gerda E. - Application 840046 (Reel 27, Frame 931)
      - Hughes, Thomas K. - Application 840047 (Reel 27, Frame 960)
      - Reimer, Gregory L. - Application 840048 (Reel 27, Frame 990)
      - Bidani, Akhil - Application 840049 (Reel 27, Frame 1018)
      - Clack, James W. - Application 840050 (Reel 27, Frame 1059)
      - LeFever, Ann - Application 840051 (Reel 27, Frame 1085)
      - Syverud, Scott A. - Application 840052 (Reel 27, Frame 1118)
      - Wessale, Jerry L. - Application 840053 (Reel 27, Frame 1148)